carpricesecrets.com 2015-06-13

# CarPriceSecrets.com - Privacy Policy

Welcome to CarPriceSecrets.com (the “Site”). Your privacy is important to us.

We provide this statement explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available through a link on all of our pages.

## Collection of Information

The Site currently collects personally identifiable information in one of two ways: (1) through your voluntary submission of a quote request form or (2) through your voluntary submission of a “contact us,” “get more information,” or other similar form available on the Site. When you request a quote, the types of information that we collect in conjunction with a quote request may include your name, address, phone number, email address and information regarding the particular vehicle(s) that you are interested in. You must provide all required fields of information for your request to be processed. The types of information we collect on the “contact us,” “get more information,” or other similar forms may include your name, dealership name and address, phone number, and email address.

The Site also passively collects information about you through the use of cookies and other technical means. Cookies are small text files that reside on your computer's hard drive. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you may configure your browser to reject them, but certain features of the Site may not function properly or at all as a result. In addition, our Web servers automatically collect information about your computer and the Web browser that you are using, including your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.

## Third Party Information Collection

Third parties may collect information about you and your use of the Site through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies. For example, we may work with third party advertising networks that use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this Site and other Web sites in order to provide targeted advertisements to you across their networks of Web sites (which may include this Site). These third parties may also use this information for determining or predicting the characteristics and preferences of their respective network audiences, for measuring the effectiveness of their advertising, and for other purposes. Also, our third-party service providers may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites, mobile websites and/or mobile applications across your various devices, in order to provide content and advertisements about goods and services of interest to you across those various devices.

If you would like to obtain more information about the practices of some of these parties, or if you would like to make choices about their use of your information, please click here:

<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

More information and additional consumer choice options may be found here:

<http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

## How Our Quote Request Process Works

When you fill out our quote request form, we match you with dealers in our affiliated network located in your area. We then transfer your name, phone number, street address, email address and any additional information you provide to these affiliated dealers. If we cannot find an affiliated dealer in your area, we transfer your information to a third-party provider, which will process your request through its own dealer network. In either case, a dealer representative should contact you by phone or email to discuss your car quote request. After the initial contact or during any other subsequent contact, you may inform the dealer you no longer wish to be contacted by him or her. It is solely the dealer’s responsibility to comply with your request. Similarly, if we transfer your information to a third-party provider in order to carry out your request, you may also be contacted by that provider. You may inform the third-party provider you no longer wish to be contacted. It is solely the third-party provider’s responsibility to comply with your request.

## Use and Sharing of Information

We may use and/or disclose personally identifiable information you submit through the Site in the following ways:

  1. ### Requests

We may use and disclose personally identifiable information as necessary to carry out your requests. For example, if you submit a quote request, we may share the personally identifiable information that you provide in the manner described above in the “How Our Quote Request Process Works” paragraph.
  2. ### Reporting

We may use and disclose personally identifiable information to provide various types of reporting to the affiliated dealers and/or other third-party providers that we submit your quote requests to. In those instances, those parties would have already received such information.
  3. ### Third Party Sales Representatives

We use third party sales representatives, including our affiliated newspaper and broadcast partners, to sign up affiliated dealers in certain areas. In the course of working with these affiliated dealers, these Sales Representatives may have access to the personally identifiable information that you provide.
  4. ### Communications

We may use personally identifiable information to communicate with you regarding our services and other services that may be of interest to you. For example, when you submit a quote request, you may receive the following email notifications from us: (1) if your car quote request was processed successfully, we will give you information about the affiliated dealer(s) to whom we sent your request ; (2) if we cannot find an affiliated dealer that is able to fulfill your request, we may give you information about the third-party provider to whom we sent your request ; and (3) if your car quote request could not be fulfilled by an affiliated dealer or a third-party provider, we may refer you to one of our online partners. We, and in some instances, our Sales Representatives, also may contact you to learn more about your experiences in using the Site and our service. With respect to any commercial email marketing from us, you will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from such communications at any time.
  5. ### Service Providers

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third-party agents, consultants, and contractors that perform services on our behalf, but only for such purposes.
  6. ### Legal Reasons

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties: (a) when required by law or legal process, (b) to investigate illegal activity or unauthorized use of Site, or (c) in connection with the sale of all or a part of our business.

With respect to information collected passively through technical means, we use this information for a variety of reasons, including but not limited to, Site administration, troubleshooting, performing statistical analyses of user behavior, and for development purposes. For example, cookies may be used to measure traffic, collect statistical information (such as which pages of the Site are visited most often by users) and to make your visit more pleasant (by remembering who you are when you return to the Site and by pre-populating forms on the Site with your information so you don't have to re-type it).

In addition to the practices described above, we reserve the right to use and share with any third party non-personally identifying information (in aggregate or other form) collected through your use of the Site for any reason.

Although we take steps to help prevent the misuse of your information, after any information is provided to third parties, we do not and cannot control their subsequent use or disclosure of such information and we are not responsible for their use.

## Accessing or Changing Information

If you wish to access, verify the accuracy of, correct, or change the personally identifiable information you have submitted via the Site, please contact us via email. To protect your privacy, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## Security

We have implemented mechanisms to help keep your personally identifiable information secure in our databases. For example, we limit internal access to such information only to those of our authorized personnel who need such access to perform operations associated with the performance or maintenance of this Site. Despite these precautions, however, we cannot and do not guarantee absolute security for the information we store or the information you transmit through the Site. Please note that information transmitted through email and Web site forms on this Site is not secure from access by third parties.

## Children's Guidelines

This Site is not directed to, or intended for use by, individuals under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children younger than 13 years old.

## Links

The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of Web sites that are linked to or from this Site. Use of any personally identifiable information provided to any such Web site will be governed by that Web site's privacy statement.

## Notification of Changes

If this privacy statement materially changes, the new privacy statement will be posted on the Site and identified as “Updated.” Your continued use of the Site after such changes have been posted shall signify acceptance of the revised privacy statement.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us via email.

Last updated: November 6, 2014
